metalasfuck.net 2015-12-30

# Privacy Policy | Metal as Fuck

1\. How is personal information collected? 

Metal as Fuck is the world's leading community of metal fans. In order to provide customers with a quality service, we offer our customers the ability to sign up as a community member, interact with other members, subscribe to our newsletter, enter competitions and (soon) to also purchase tickets to events online through our site.

In order to provide these services, Metal as Fuck collects personal information about customers. Collection of this information will occur at the time you enter a competition, make a purchase or when you register as a member of the site through our website.

**2\. What personal information does Metal as Fuck collect and why?  
**  
If you purchase tickets, register as a member or enter a competition through MetalasFuck.net, we need to collect personal information about you, including your name, address, email address and telephone number(s).

The reason we need this information is so we can contact you to send you a prize, or to notify you in the case of an event cancellation or change of event details. We also need some of this information in order to process your online credit card payment, which occurs through secure payment gateways.

Metal as Fuck will also provide you with the opportunity to receive special offers and promotions if you wish to do so. Even if you initially choose to subscribe to receive special offers, you may also unsubscribe or resubscribe at a later stage - all you need to do is visit your profile page and edit your information. Either that, or contact Metal as Fuck through the contact details at #12 below.

**3\. Will personal information be given to anyone else?  
**  
Metal as Fuck will never sell or trade personal information about you to or with third parties. Metal as Fuck will only disclose information about you, if you have given your consent, so that you can be provided with promotional material and special offers. Otherwise, Metal as Fuck will only disclose personal information if this is required by law or permitted under the Privacy Act.

**4\. Security of personal information  
**  
Metal as Fuck protects the personal information it collects in a secure database, which can only be accessed by employees with the highest security clearance. Metal as Fuck employees are required, as a condition of their employment, to treat personal information held by Metal as Fuck as confidential, and to maintain the confidentiality of that personal information.

**5\. Non-customer information  
**  
Sometimes, Metal as Fuck needs to collect personal information about individuals who are not customers. This will usually arise where we collect the name and business contact details of our clients. Metal as Fuck's policy is to only use personal information collected from non-customers for the main business purpose for which it was collected.

**6\. Access and correction  
**  
Under the Privacy Act, you have a right to seek access to information that Metal as Fuck holds about you. You also have the right to ask us to correct information about you, which is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. As a Metal as Fuck, you are able to access or correct the personal information that Metal as Fuck - simply by logging onto our website at [http://www.metalasfuck.net](http://www.metalasfuck.net/ "http://www.metalasfuck.net") and accessing your personal profile. Both members and non-members may ask us to correct information, which is inaccurate, incomplete or out of date. To provide you with access to personal information about you, Metal as Fuck would usually provide you with a print-out of the relevant personal information from our database. If you wish to access the personal information that we hold about you, please set out your request in writing, including your phone number, and forward this to our Privacy Officer at PO Box 185, Upper Sturt, South Australia 5156 (Australia). In the interests of protecting the privacy of individuals about whom we hold personal information, we will require that you verify your identity by enclosing a certified copy of a form of identification such as a current driver's licence or passport with your written request (this will be returned to you after your identity has been verified). If you wish to change personal information that is inaccurate or out-of-date, please contact our Privacy Officer, using the contact details at #12 below, with your request for correction. Metal as Fuck's policy is to consider any requests for access or correction within 21 days. Ordinarily, Metal as Fuck will not charge you for the cost of providing this type of access to these records. However, if we do propose to charge you, we will advise you of the relevant charge before we provide you with access.

**7\. Further notes regarding online privacy  
**  
This Privacy Policy is part of the terms of use for our website. When you deal with Metal as Fuck, whether online or otherwise, Metal as Fuck takes its privacy obligations seriously. We will use personal information collected online to provide you with our products and services (eg to process your online purchases), to contact you in the case of an event cancellation or a change of venue, and if you agree, for Metal as Fuck's marketing purposes. Other matters specific to FasterLouder.com.au's handling of personal information online are set out below.

**8\. Online collection of personal and non-personal information  
**  
As outlined at point 1 of this Privacy Policy, we collect personal information through our website. For example, Metal as Fuck will collect personal information online from customers when they register as a member of Metal as Fuck or when they purchase through our website. Our website also collects other information - some of this is personal information, and some is not. For each visitor to our website, our server automatically recognises and stores the visitor's domain name, but not their email address. In addition, our website uses cookies. Most web browsers are set by default to accept cookies. However, if you do not wish to receive any cookies you may set your browser to either prompt or refuse cookies. Please note that rejecting cookies will disable your browser from purchasing tickets from our website once this is functional, and it will restrict the functionality of the website as a whole. We also use cookies for tracking the statistics of our website. This allows us to better understand our users and improve the layout and functionality of our website.

**9\. Online disclosures  
**  
To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, Metal as Fuck has relationships with other companies that we allow to place advertisements on our web pages. If you visit our website, advertisement server companies may collect information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information.

**10\. Secure Online Transactions  
**  
If you make a purchase through our website, we process your credit card details securely over the Internet using an accredited Internet payment security system. With the combination of encryption provided by a third party and a secure browser at your end, we take all measures to ensure that your credit card and anonymity are protected when you purchase online.

11\. Links to other websites

Sometimes our website contains links to third party websites, for your convenience and information. When you access a non-MetalasFuck.net website, please understand that Metal as Fuck is not responsible for the privacy practices of that site. We suggest that you review the privacy policies of each site you visit.

**12\. Additional privacy information and how to contact Metal as Fuck  
**  
Metal as Fuck may change its Privacy Policy at any time. Metal as Fuck will make available this policy to anyone who requests it. For further information about privacy issues and the protection of privacy visit the Australian Federal Privacy Commissioner's website at [www.privacy.gov.au](http://www.privacy.gov.au/ "www.privacy.gov.au"). If you feel that Metalasfuck.net is not complying with this Privacy Policy, or if you have other privacy concerns, please contact our Privacy Officer (using the following contact details):   
 by email   
by letter to PO Box 185, Upper Sturt SA  5156 AUSTRALIA
